# **OLATUNJI OLUWAPELUMI SAMSON**

## Fullstack software developer

To effectively develop any organization I work with by utilizing my acquired skills, experience, knowledge in software development, ability to pick up new technology and learn fast, working diligently to ultimately contribute my quota so as to fulfil organizational objectives and achieve managerial goals and targets.

### **EDUCATION**

#### 2014-2017

(BSc) Computer Science and Information Technology

Class of Degree: **\$econd Class Upper (2:1)**Bowen University, Iwo, Osun State.

### **WORK HISTORY**

## (2018-2020) ICT IN\$TRUCTOR

Smiley Kids Montessori / Smiley International School

- Instructed pupils and staff on operations of computer and how to code using scratch.
- Managed the school website and portal.
- Personally saw to the good care of the electronic devices at the ICT lab, the projector, the ISP (routers and access points).

#### (FEB. 2021 – PRESENT) FULLSTACK ENGINEER

Stutern (Remote)

- API design, code review, solving algorithms, debug problems, writing standard codes.
- Breakdown tasks, using github personally and as a team, project design expectations, general software work flow, and progress management on tasks via Trello

## (April 2021 – PRESENT) FRONTEND ENGINEER (INTERN)

Payfrontier (Remote)

- Mostly contributed to the frontend of their application.
- Learnt teamwork on version control system

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, NodeJs, ExpressJs, REST, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Git/Github, Agile development practices.

HOME ADDRESS: 14, Oladunni Street, Glory Estate, Ifako, Gbagada.

PHONE: 08166266326 EMAIL: samsontunj@gmail.com

GITHUB: https://github.com/olat95 | PORTFOLIO:

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/pelumi-olatunji-024337154